# **LANA ILIĆ** JUNIOR DEVELOPER



# PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Young professional with an industry experience building websites and web applications. Specializes in Java language, and has experience working with React.js, HTML5, CSS. Simultaneously finishing studies with a major in Information Systems and Technology at Faculty of Organizational Sciences, where also honored with a scholarship for extremely gifted students. Constantly working on improving knowledge, skills and experience in various areas of the IT industry, such as web design, object-oriented programming and databases.

Open for new challenges, opportunities and achievements.

#### ACADEMIC BACKGROUND

# FACULTY OF ORGANIZATIONAL SCIENCES UNIVERSITY OF BELGRADE

#### Bachelor of engineering | Sep 2018 - present

- Course: Information Systems and Technologies - study program aimed at acquiring the latest knowledge and skills in the field of information systems and technologies, mastering the latest methods and techniques with a multidisciplinary view.
- Avg. grade: 9.3/10

#### LANGUAGES

Serbian (Native) English (C2) German (B1)

#### TECH-STACKS

Java(Primary) MySQL React.js Javascript HTML5 Wordpress CSS Photoshop

# **REACH ME AT:**

- Crnotravska 11b, Belgrade, Serbia
- □ lana.ilic99@gmail.com
- in https://www.linkedin.com/in/lana-ilic/
- https://github.com/li20180014
- +381 64 1202 171

#### PROFESSIONAL HISTORY

#### JUNIOR DEVELOPER

# Kalyanamay | December 2020 - present

- Responsible for creating the design and appearance, as well as developing functionalities of user-friendly, responsive websites using ecommerce platforms.
- Skills gained: Web Design · HTML · CSS · Javascript(Basic)

# DIGITAL MARKETING SPECIALIST

# Kalyanamay | May 2020 - December 2020

- Specialized in formulating strategies to build a digital connection with consumers, including planning the ongoing company presence on social
- Launching online advertisements to increase company and brand awareness.
- Skills gained: Digital Marketing · Social Media · Critical thinking · Listening · Communication · Presentation skills